Can I just say one point on
therapy, right?
We all talk about sort of
medicine now, right?
And it's sort of become
depersonalized
and you go in, you're like a
number in the cog
of however many patients,
you know, therapy.
We did a survey study on
therapy
and we've looked at all of
our shoulder replacements.
We said, you know, how
important is this to you?
And 98% of patients said the
therapist
was a huge impact on their
outcome.
And 95% of them said that
their therapist changed
what they did, how they did
it.
And it's like having a
hairdresser.
They talk to you, they
listen to you.
It's the company you need.
So whether you're remote in
telemedicine and therapy,
whether you're in person,
it's a huge factor
in everything that we do as
surgeons.